We make chicken wings but we leave out the calories.
Every time I make fried chicken wings
I have to hear wang wang
we want healthy
Y'all do be whining
Off rip I'm gonna deviate
add a little bit of olive oil
because they're gonna air fry right
So I
need a little bit of like oil
as a conduit right
If it comes out fucked up
it's on me right
Another one of my brothers who
didn't say anything about measurements
so we're gonna measure with our souls
Also went in with some pepper
some garlic powder
some onion powder
some paprika
some cayenne pepper
some lemon pepper seasoning
This is from my garden
so this is gonna be an extra love here
A little bit of that elbow ash for a good measure
and some baking powder
Give that a toss
I'm gonna
put that in a 400 degree air fryer
Air fryer 20 minutes
Flipping halfway through
I let these go for
35 minutes
They are not crispy
Is that my fault
for adding the oil
It could be my fault
so let's just judge these off of taste
The flavor's all there
Jeez Louise
there's juices in them
So
I essentially just made
a roasted chicken wing
A very good roasted chicken wing
Don't add any oil